{
    "id": "7debcf8d2b724828be4685080599155a",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the book ……………………",
            "description": "When the object of the preposition is the relative pronoun that, the preposition is always placed at the end.",
            "answers": [
                "that you were looking for",
                "for that you were looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6464622bca204d8fabc5f22a65323a9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………… the top of his class.",
            "description": "We use at to speak of things at rest.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b60be7ad1fe640918733c6d3d9857e96"
        },
        {
            "question": "The snake crawled ………………… its hole.",
            "description": "We use into to speak of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0988bf988bee42c281aba7a0c4ee71ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where I live in",
                "in that I live",
                "I live in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b1f4b2624b34fde88b47f3fa79e4840"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat sprang …………………. the table.",
            "description": "We use upon to speak of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bff7c652e4e94f028e7a498f8c53ba31"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked …………………… the end of the street.",
            "description": "Until and till are used to talk about time to talk about distance we use to or up to.",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "till",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10c2f95a59b64b16b18c27bae814377c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I slept …………………. 9 o’clock.",
            "description": "We use till to talk about time.",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "up to",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aeaeeadbe2dd445a839ce5c5b1b78f28"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t eaten anything …………………. yesterday.",
            "description": "Since is used to indicate some point of time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4c261ed68624005915842cfcd12abd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been ill …………………… many days.",
            "description": "For is used with a period of time.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb7488e6784f4c48a31508f36ebb39c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not seen him …………………. last week.",
            "description": "Since is used to indicate some point of time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "85e76f710251485898c4d09c4975703e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will join work ……………………. tomorrow.",
            "description": "From is also used with a noun or phrase indicating a point of time, but unlike since it is used with all the tenses.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "023d6f68fbf045a4a35c497aecbd1965"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. his children, his nephews and nieces were present there.",
            "description": "Besides means in addition to.",
            "answers": [
                "Besides",
                "Beside"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05630c5cb33b4f27b99129e9708eb310"
        }
    ]
}